--------- beginning of main
07-13 00:30:08.052  1646  2236 W AiAiEcho: LyftNotificationParser Ridesharing ETA not enabled
07-13 00:30:08.052  1646  2236 I AiAiEcho: SmartspaceNotificationPredictor no parser can handle this notification or notification is invalid
07-13 00:30:09.044  1646  2236 W AiAiEcho: LyftNotificationParser Ridesharing ETA not enabled
07-13 00:30:09.044  1646  2236 I AiAiEcho: SmartspaceNotificationPredictor no parser can handle this notification or notification is invalid
07-13 00:30:09.049   541   541 I adbd    : adbd service requested 'shell,v2:export ANDROID_LOG_TAGS=''; exec logcat '-d''
